Guide to the Ron Offen Papers 1944-2007
University of Chicago Library
- Series III: Free Lunch: A Poetry Miscellany
  - Subseries 4: Expenses [RESTRICTED]
    - Expenses, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Expenses, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Expenses, 1996-1997 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Expenses, 1996-1997 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Series IV: Audio-Visual
  - Cassette Tape; Interview for Brando, undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - DVD; Andidris Goodwin Lecture, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Videocassette; Ron Offen, Last Celebration of Leon Duprey, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Videocassette; Jack Ridl, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Videocassettes; Aplon, Brown, Dorman, 1997; Lynn Manning, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Videocassettes; Kim Blaeser, 2004; Paul Roesce, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Videocassettes; Ruth Daigon, 1997; Taylor Graham at Crown Valley Library, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Videocassettes; Ron Offen, Madame Sostro: The Dream Merchant, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Videocassettes; Barry Spacks at Crown Valley Library, 1997; Charles H. Webb at Crown Valley Library, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 1)